webadvantage.net 2008-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Web Ad.vantage

[Home](http://www.webadvantage.net/ "Browse to: Home") | Privacy Policy 

No information is sold or released to anyone about visitors to this site or customers of WebAdvantage.net, Inc. without prior consent. In other words, no information is released to anyone unless you give permission first. This includes e-mail registration to mailing lists, or information requests. A user does not have to supply any personal information unless they decide to complete an information request or at their own will in sending email to employees or departments at WebAd.vantage, Inc.

WebAdvantage.net, Inc. does not attempt to collect personal information from children. If children do send personal information to WebAd.vantage, Inc., such as sending e-mail, filling out online forms,etc., the information is deleted. Note that WebAdvantage.net, Inc. cannot always determine that a user is a child.

Aggregate reports for website visitors are generated. These reports do not contain any personally identifiable information.

Internet ‘cookies’ are used on this website to eliminate certain content, such as pop-up boxes, from being served to the same visitor more than one time.

When visiting any Internet site your unique address called an “IP address” is recorded. WebAdvantage.net, Inc. does not release any information about the collection of this address to any third party except under court order. Web Ad.vantage, Inc. archives the log files in order to create aggregate statistical reports, detect errors at the website, and for security reasons. The log files are eventually deleted.

To have personal information removed from the WebAdvantage.net, Inc. database contact [privacy@webadvantage.net](mailto:privacy@webadvantage.net).

> I am honored to have the chance to work with someone that is truly outstanding! 

**\--Stephen Coakley,  
President**  
Rapid Registration, Inc.

06/12/2008 

#### [Did Lycos Dump Ask.com for Yahoo?](http://www.webadvantage.net/webadblog/did-lycos-dump-askcom-for-yahoo-674)

In a recent review of rankings for a client, our astute search specialist noticed a new trend in Lycos search. The search rankings from Lycos usually are a close match to those from ASK their search partner. Recently, however, the results have shown...   [read more](http://www.webadvantage.net/webadblog/did-lycos-dump-askcom-for-yahoo-674)

06/11/2008 

#### [Online Marketing to Boomers and Beyond](http://www.webadvantage.net/webadblog/online-marketing-to-boomers-and-beyond-670)

A recent survey conducted by JWTBoom and Third Age, of more than 1800 online Boomers (defined by the surveyors as users aged 40+) revealed some surprising insights about the online behaviors of Boomers with regard to social networking, online...   [read more](http://www.webadvantage.net/webadblog/online-marketing-to-boomers-and-beyond-670)

06/09/2008 

#### [Social Media Is Opening Up](http://www.webadvantage.net/webadblog/social-media-is-opening-up-668)

I hate having a separate account profile for every single social media website in which I participate. In an average day I log onto (with different account info!) what I consider the bare minimum of social sites that I must maintain: Facebook,...   [read more](http://www.webadvantage.net/webadblog/social-media-is-opening-up-668)
